<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <!-- Room Names -->
  <roomname.outofbounds>Out of Bounds Area</roomname.outofbounds>
  <roomname.rooftops>Rooftops</roomname.rooftops>
  <roomname.sewers>Sewers</roomname.sewers>
  <roomname.streets>Streets</roomname.streets>
  <roomname.slums>Slums</roomname.slums>
  <roomname.factory>Factory</roomname.factory>
  <roomname.factoryrooftop>Factory rooftop</roomname.factoryrooftop>
  <roomname.hospital>Hospital</roomname.hospital>
  <roomname.hospitalrooftop>Hospital rooftop</roomname.hospitalrooftop>
  <roomname.shop>Shop</roomname.shop>
  <roomname.brigrooftop>Brig rooftop</roomname.brigrooftop>
  <roomname.divingarmory>Diving armory</roomname.divingarmory>
  <roomname.motel>Motel</roomname.motel>
  <roomname.motelrooftop>Motel rooftop</roomname.motelrooftop>
  <roomname.huskstatue>Husk statue</roomname.huskstatue>
  <roomname.damborder>Dam border</roomname.damborder>
  <roomname.dam>Dam</roomname.dam>
  <roomname.damoffices>Dam offices</roomname.damoffices>
  <roomname.damrooftop>Dam rooftop</roomname.damrooftop>
  <roomname.damcafeteria>Dam cafeteria</roomname.damcafeteria>
  <roomname.damgreenhouse>Dam greenhouse</roomname.damgreenhouse>
  <roomname.security>Security</roomname.security>
  <roomname.janitorialcloset>Janitorial closet</roomname.janitorialcloset>
  <roomname.janitorialquarters>Janitorial quarters</roomname.janitorialquarters>
  <roomname.engineersquarters>Engineers quarters</roomname.engineersquarters>
  <roomname.captainsquarters>Captains quarters</roomname.captainsquarters>
  <roomname.dammaintenanceshafts>Dam maintenance shafts</roomname.dammaintenanceshafts>
  <roomname.reactorcontrolroom>Reactor control room</roomname.reactorcontrolroom>
  <roomname.dambasin>Dam basin</roomname.dambasin>
  <roomname.clownroom>Clown room</roomname.clownroom>
  
  <character.spitroach>Spitroach</character.spitroach>
  
  <Override>
  <!-- Mayor Job -->
  <jobname.captain>Mayor</jobname.captain>
  <jobdescription.captain>You are the ruler (probably because of your impervious to damage liver and lungs) of this place, but no one rules alone. You will rely on enforcers to make your word be followed, the divers to keep the local fauna at bay, the medical staff to keep all healthy, the engineers to keep the dam and its reactor working and the laborers with producing crucial supplies.</jobdescription.captain>
  <!-- Engineer -->
  <jobname.engineer>Engineer</jobname.engineer>
  <jobdescription.engineer>A highly trained and valuable professional responsable with maintaining the dam and its reactor. Security will often be busy, so you have been trusted with a handgun, do not be reckless with it, instead use it mainly to keep saboteurs away.</jobdescription.engineer>
  <!-- Enforcer -->
  <jobname.securityofficer>Enforcer</jobname.securityofficer>
  <jobdescription.securityofficer>As the name suggests, your main responsability is enforcing the law of the land. You also have to keep the residents safe, that unfortunately includes the peasents. If someone ever becomes a threat, it is desirable to arrest them if possible, after all, you are not getting paid per kill.</jobdescription.securityofficer>
  <!-- Medical Doctor -->
  <jobname.medicaldoctor>Medical Doctor</jobname.medicaldoctor>
  <jobdescription.medicaldoctor>Although usually taken for granted, doctors play an important role, possessing the required skill to treat injured or unconscious crewmembers. Their skills can also be useful for creating various non-medicinal chemicals.</jobdescription.medicaldoctor>
  <!-- Assistant -->
  <jobname.assistant>Convict</jobname.assistant>
  <jobdescription.assistant>Sentenced to a life in prison. No longer worried about following the law, as soon as you break out of these shackles, all hell will break loose.</jobdescription.assistant>
  <!-- Laborer Job -->
  <jobname.mechanic>Laborer</jobname.mechanic>
  <jobdescription.mechanic>Has all non-event specific recipes unlocked. Work at the factory to refine raw materials into equipment, weapons, tools, ammo and armor. From time to time have a drink with the lads and plan an uprising agaisnt your oppressors. We work to earn the right to work to earn the right to give ourselves the right to buy ourselves the right to live to earn the right to die.</jobdescription.mechanic>
  </Override>
  
  <!-- Greenskin Job -->
  <jobname.greenskinjob>Greenskin</jobname.greenskinjob>
  <jobdescription.greenskinjob>You are a kind of amphibious nimble critter that like playing games with their prey. Put masks on humans to turn them into goblins. Hide in goblin crates to regenerate.</jobdescription.greenskinjob>
  <!-- Janitor Job -->
  <jobname.janitor>Janitor</jobname.janitor>
  <jobdescription.janitor>A firm believer of the broken windows theory. Discard items you find on the floor, spray any dirt away, do pest control with your flamer and get paid little, but still more than whatever the factory workers are paid. Occasionally attempt an uprising with the laborers.</jobdescription.janitor>
  <!-- Clown Job -->
  <jobname.clown>Clown</jobname.clown>
  <jobdescription.clown>The only rule is there are no rules! Well almost. Do your best at making security hate you and (optionally) make the residents love you.</jobdescription.clown>
  <!-- Foreman Job -->
  <jobname.foreman>Head Engineer</jobname.foreman>
  <jobdescription.foreman>The mayor will often be too busy to watch over the dam, and that is where you come in. You will work together with the engineers and janitors around to make sure the dam and its reactors are working neatly at all times. If the situation damands it, you can also temporarily serve as an additional security officer.</jobdescription.foreman>
  <!-- Researcher Job -->
  <jobname.researcher>Researcher</jobname.researcher>
  <jobdescription.researcher>Aside from working as a Medical Doctor if the times come, you will also be mainly conducting often unethical research with the aim of producing antidotes to infections by using your blood sampler on infected and later refining your live samples into antidotes in a medical fabricator.</jobdescription.researcher>
  <!-- Diver Job -->
  <jobname.diver>Diver</jobname.diver>
  <jobdescription.diver>Expert in diving and hunting. Your main task is keeping the local fauna in check with your guns and to mine with your plasma cutter. If the situation calls for it, you can also temporarily work as just an additional security officer.</jobdescription.diver>
  <!-- Bodyguard Job -->
  <jobname.bodyguard>Bodyguard</jobname.bodyguard>
  <jobdescription.bodyguard>Hired, trained and armed to keep the VIP safe at all costs. Mission failure will result in subject termination.</jobdescription.bodyguard>
  <!-- Nukie Job -->
  <jobname.jet>Jovian Elite Trooper</jobname.jet>
  <jobdescription.jet>Jovian Elite Troops. Destroy that dam and kill every single bastard inside who isn't allied with the separatists.</jobdescription.jet>
  <!-- Wizard Job -->
  <jobname.wizard>Wizard</jobname.wizard>
  <jobdescription.wizard>A master at casting spells, your main objective is to cause chaos and mayhem using magic. You are free to be good or evil.</jobdescription.wizard>
  <!-- MERCS Job -->
  <jobname.mercs>MERCS Member</jobname.mercs>
  <jobdescription.mercs>Mobile Emergency Rescue and Combat Squad. A highly trained paramilitary working for Nexpharma. Restore order in the dam and protect it. Mission failure will result in subject termination.</jobdescription.mercs>
  <jobname.mercsevil>MERC Squadder</jobname.mercsevil>
  <jobdescription.mercsevil>Mobile Emergency Rescue and Combat Squad. A highly trained paramilitary working for Nexpharma. Explode the reactor and kill any personnel related to the dam. Mission failure will result in subject termination.</jobdescription.mercsevil>
  
  <!-- Immune Afflictions -->
  <afflictionname.antibiotics>Antibiotics</afflictionname.antibiotics>
  <afflictiondescription.antibiotics>Antibiotics are circulating in the bloodstream and fending off infections, especially those of a bacterial nature.</afflictiondescription.antibiotics>
  <afflictionname.immuneresponse>Immune-response</afflictionname.immuneresponse>
  <afflictiondescription.immuneresponse>The body is working hard at fighting an infection.</afflictiondescription.immuneresponse>
  <afflictionname.fever>Fever</afflictionname.fever>
  <afflictiondescription.fever>Fights infections, but too high body temperatures can be counterproductive. Treatable with Stabilozine.</afflictiondescription.fever>
  <!-- Misc Afflictions -->
  <afflictionname.despawn>Despawn Decay</afflictionname.despawn>
  <afflictiondescription.despawn>The corpse is decaying away and will soon despawn.</afflictiondescription.despawn>
  <afflictionname.bloodlust>Bloodlust</afflictionname.bloodlust>
  <afflictiondescription.bloodlust>Regeneration, resistance, immunity to illness and greatly increased melee strength.</afflictiondescription.bloodlust>
  <afflictionname.pulmonaryemphysema>Pulmonary Emphysema</afflictionname.pulmonaryemphysema>
  <afflictiondescription.pulmonaryemphysema>The lung, due to major alveoli rupture, is unable to absorb oxygen into the bloodstream.</afflictiondescription.pulmonaryemphysema>
  <afflictionname.bacterialgangrene>Bacterial Gangrene</afflictionname.bacterialgangrene>
  <afflictiondescription.bacterialgangrene.dormant>Dormant bacterial gangrene. Treat the bite wounds or bleeding now and this will heal by itself.</afflictiondescription.bacterialgangrene.dormant>
  <afflictiondescription.bacterialgangrene.active>Active bacterial gangrene. Apply antibiotics or wash with ethanol before this worsens and bacterial sepsis occurs.</afflictiondescription.bacterialgangrene.active>
  <!-- Disease Afflictions -->
  <afflictionname.fluinfection>Flu Infection</afflictionname.fluinfection>
  <afflictiondescription.fluinfection>Vry contagious pulmonary infection. Usually not lethal on its own. Causes shortness of air.</afflictiondescription.fluinfection>
  <afflictionname.bacterialinfection>Bacterial Infection</afflictionname.bacterialinfection>
  <afflictiondescription.bacterialinfection>A broad unspecific bacterial infection. Usually not lethal on its own. Treatable with Broad-spectrum Antibiotics</afflictiondescription.bacterialinfection>
  <afflictionname.tbinfection>Tuberculosis Infection</afflictionname.tbinfection>
  <afflictiondescription.tbinfection>A very lethal bacterial lung infection, also highly transmissible. If untreated, will very likely result in death. Treatable with Broad-spectrum Antibiotics</afflictiondescription.tbinfection>
  <afflictionname.anthraxinfection>Anthrax Infection</afflictionname.anthraxinfection>
  <afflictiondescription.anthraxinfection>A very lethal bacterial infection found in corpses. If untreated, will very likely result in death. Treatable with Broad-spectrum Antibiotics</afflictiondescription.anthraxinfection>
  
  <Override>
  <entityname.ironhelmet>Makeshift Helmet</entityname.ironhelmet><!-- Iron Helmet now is called Makeshift Helmet -->
  <entityname.orangejumpsuit1>Lead-lined Overalls</entityname.orangejumpsuit1>
  <entitydescription.captainspipe>Used for smoking pipe tabacco. Somehow heals damage and bloodloss at an impressive rate. Causes about as much lung damage as an entire pack of cigars.</entitydescription.captainspipe>
  <entitydescription.cigar>A finely crafted cigar. Somehow heals damage and bloodloss. Intense and frequent use may cause hard to reverse lung damage.</entitydescription.cigar>
  <entitydescription.rum>A fine liquor made from raptor bane juice or pomegrenade extract. Heals husk infection when drunk. Can be poured on wounds to clear gangrene. Can be used as a low quality generator fuel.</entitydescription.rum>
  <entitydescription.ethanol>Medical alcohol used as an ingredient in the manufacture of various medicines. Drinking while on duty is not advised. Can be poured on wounds to clear gangrene. Can be used as a low quality generator fuel.</entitydescription.ethanol>
  <entitydescription.fertilizer>Carefully tended Europan soil guaranteed to give your plant the best living conditions. Can be used as a high quality generator fuel. Keep away from fire or heat.</entitydescription.fertilizer>
  <entitydescription.stabilozine>Used as an ingredient in the manufacture of various medicines. On its own, can be used to slow down the effects of most toxins and lower fever.</entitydescription.stabilozine>
  <entitydescription.adrenaline>A naturally occurring hormone. When consumed awakens anyone unconcious. Used to manufacture medicine or combat stimulants.</entitydescription.adrenaline>
  <entitydescription.piratebodyarmor>Only craftable by rebel leaders. A set of body armor, partially fashioned out of improvised materials by the Jovian Separatists. It's heavier than it looks.</entitydescription.piratebodyarmor>
  <entitydescription.flamer>Only craftable by janitors. An incendiary weapon that fires a stream of burning welding fuel. Particularly effective with incendium fuel tanks.</entitydescription.flamer>
  <entitydescription.handcuffs>Useful for restraining problem players. Whilst a player is alive and detained, they will be dragged at full speed.</entitydescription.handcuffs>
  <!--<entitydescription.replaceme></entitydescription.replaceme>-->
  </Override>
  
  <!-- Combustion Fuel -->
  <entityname.combustionfuel>Combustion Fuel</entityname.combustionfuel>
  <entitydescription.combustionfuel>A high quality combustion fuel for generators. Keep away from fire or heat.</entitydescription.combustionfuel>
  <!-- Trash Bag -->
  <entityname.trashbag>Trash Bag</entityname.trashbag>
  <entitydescription.trashbag>Only craftable by janitors. Utilizes non-euclidean space and mysterious alchemical processes to, after having 20 items put inside it, turn into 8 scrap.</entitydescription.trashbag>
  <!-- Nexcredit -->
  <entityname.money>Nexcredit</entityname.money>
  <entitydescription.money>Nexcredits (TM) can be exchanged for goods at Nexshops (TM). This message was sponsored by Nexpharma (TM).</entitydescription.money>
  <!-- Counterfeit Nexcredit -->
  <entityname.fakemoney>Counterfeit Nexcredit</entityname.fakemoney>
  <entitydescription.fakemoney>Any human can easily tell these are fake, but they can still spoof Nexshops. Very much illegal, do not let security catch you with one of these!</entitydescription.fakemoney>
  <!-- Nexcase -->
  <entityname.moneycase>Nexcase</entityname.moneycase>
  <entitydescription.moneycase>Money? I love money! Do you love money? This Nexcase (TM) can be used to temporarily store Nexcredits (TM).</entitydescription.moneycase>
  <!-- Portable Generator -->
  <entityname.portablegenerator>Portable Generator</entityname.portablegenerator>
  <entitydescription.portablegenerator>A small portable combustion generator for emergencies. Can be hooked up to as many as five appliances. Not recommended to directly connect it to the main electrical grid due to small power output. Keep out of water.</entitydescription.portablegenerator>
  <!-- Foldable Chair -->
  <entityname.foldablechair>Foldable Chair</entityname.foldablechair>
  <entitydescription.foldablechair>A simple foldable metal chair. Now you can sit almost wherever you want with this! Surprisingly sturdy, sturdy enough to, say, lethally whack someone in the head with.</entitydescription.foldablechair>
  <entityname.foldablechairoxygenite>Oxygenite Foldable Chair</entityname.foldablechairoxygenite>
  <entitydescription.foldablechairoxygenite>A foldable chair that has been infused with oxygenite, granting it a powerful crit-boosted explosive attack. Extra effective at lethally whacking heads.</entitydescription.foldablechairoxygenite>
  <!-- Printer -->
  <entityname.printer>Printer</entityname.printer>
  <entitydescription.printer>An advanced ID card and clothing printer. Capable of processing plastic into ID cards or organic fiber into clothing. It can also then deconstruct them back into plastic or fiber. Finally, it can change the job of an ID card or piece of clothing.</entitydescription.printer>
  <!-- Tool Kit -->
  <entityname.toolkit>Tool Kit</entityname.toolkit>
  <entitydescription.toolkit>A portable kit containing the necessary tools to repair items or manufacture items in case of emergency. Does not require power, but fabricates slightly slower.</entitydescription.toolkit>
  <!-- Wifi Trigger -->
  <entityname.wifitrigger>Wifi Trigger</entityname.wifitrigger>
  <entitydescription.wifitrigger>A handheld device that contains an wifi component, allowing for convenient remote sending of signals.</entitydescription.wifitrigger>
  <!-- Myxotoxin -->
  <entityname.myxotoxin>Myxotoxin</entityname.myxotoxin>
  <entitydescription.myxotoxin>Minor toxin with antibiotic properties extracted from a colony of myxobacteria. Side-effects include internal damage and alcohol sensitivity. Can be further processed into ABX.</entitydescription.myxotoxin>
  <!-- Live Influenza -->
  <entityname.flusyringe>Live Influenza</entityname.flusyringe>
  <entitydescription.flusyringe>A syringe containing a live sample of influenza that was taken from someone using a blood sampler. Can be made into Influenza Antidote in a medical fabricator.</entitydescription.flusyringe>
  <!-- Influenza Antidote -->
  <entityname.fluantidote>Influenza Antidote</entityname.fluantidote>
  <entitydescription.fluantidote>A concoction of a weakened flu virus and antibodies. Quickly heals any ongoing flu infection and gives temporary immunity to it aswell.</entitydescription.fluantidote>
  <!-- Live Bacteria -->
  <entityname.bacterialsyringe>Live Bacteria</entityname.bacterialsyringe>
  <entitydescription.bacterialsyringe>A syringe containing a live sample of bacteria that was taken from someone using a blood sampler. Can be made into Broad-spectrum Antibiotics in a medical fabricator.</entitydescription.bacterialsyringe>
  <!-- Live Tuberculosis -->
  <entityname.tbsyringe>Live Tuberculosis</entityname.tbsyringe>
  <entitydescription.tbsyringe>A syringe containing a live sample of tuberculosis that was taken from someone using a blood sampler. Can be made into Broad-spectrum Antibiotics or Tuberculosis Antidote in a medical fabricator.</entitydescription.tbsyringe>
  <!-- Tuberculosis Antidote -->
  <entityname.tbantidote>Tuberculosis Antidote</entityname.tbantidote>
  <entitydescription.tbantidote>A concoction of tuberculosis parts and antibodies. Quickly heals any ongoing tuberculosis infection and gives temporary immunity to it aswell.</entitydescription.tbantidote>
  <!-- Live Anthrax -->
  <entityname.anthraxsyringe>Live Anthrax</entityname.anthraxsyringe>
  <entitydescription.anthraxsyringe>A syringe containing a live sample of anthrax that was taken from someone using a blood sampler. Can be made into Anthrax Antidote in a medical fabricator.</entitydescription.anthraxsyringe>
  <!-- Anthrax Antidote -->
  <entityname.anthraxantidote>Anthrax Antidote</entityname.anthraxantidote>
  <entitydescription.anthraxantidote>A concoction of anthrax parts and antibodies. Quickly heals any ongoing anthrax infection and gives temporary immunity to it aswell.</entitydescription.anthraxantidote>
  <!-- Blood Sampler -->
  <entityname.bloodsampler>Blood Sampler</entityname.bloodsampler>
  <entitydescription.bloodsampler>Can be used on infected people to extract a live sample of their infection. Live disease samples can be turned into their antidotes in a medical fabricator.</entitydescription.bloodsampler>
  <!-- Heal Gun -->
  <entityname.healgun>Heal Gun</entityname.healgun>
  <entitydescription.healgun>A rapid-fire pneumatic syringe gun tailored for a special high-capacity drum. Built-in health scanner. Recently attacked players receive reduced healing from this gun.</entitydescription.healgun>
  <!-- Blood Sampler -->
  <entityname.healgundrum>Heal Gun Drum</entityname.healgundrum>
  <entitydescription.healgundrum>Drum with 50 harmless healing syringes. These can heal damage, bloodloss, burns and bleeding.</entitydescription.healgundrum>
  <!-- Diving Flashlight -->
  <entityname.divingflashlight>Diving Flashlight</entityname.divingflashlight>
  <entitydescription.divingflashlight>Double the power... double the power consumption.</entitydescription.divingflashlight>
  <!-- Repair Tool -->
  <entityname.repairtool>Repair Tool</entityname.repairtool>
  <entitydescription.repairtool>All in one repair tool that can weld, wrench and screw! Use the toggle to alternate between wrench and screwdriver mode.</entitydescription.repairtool>
  <!-- Wizard Items -->
  <entityname.merasmushat>Wizard Hat</entityname.merasmushat>
  <entitydescription.merasmushat>The skull of a goat, a proper skull island topper. May explode the head of non-wizards who try to wear it.</entitydescription.merasmushat>
  <entityname.merasmusrobes>Wizard Robes</entityname.merasmusrobes>
  <entitydescription.merasmusrobes>A dark robe used by magicians. Slowly yet surely cures all ailments a wizard may have, but will burn commoners when worn.</entitydescription.merasmusrobes>
  <entityname.merasmusstaff>Wizard Staff</entityname.merasmusstaff>
  <entitydescription.merasmusstaff>A wooden staff used alongside a spellbook to cast spells.</entitydescription.merasmusstaff>
  <entityname.merasmusfireballbook>Scrungly Spellbook</entityname.merasmusfireballbook>
  <entitydescription.merasmusfireballbook>A spellbook that when equipped with a staff can be used to shoot scrungly nitroglycerin fireballs.</entitydescription.merasmusfireballbook>
  <entityname.merasmusteleportbook>Blink Spellbook</entityname.merasmusteleportbook>
  <entitydescription.merasmusteleportbook>A spellbook that when equipped with a staff can be used to teleport. Does not telefrag or deal damage.</entitydescription.merasmusteleportbook>
  <!-- Boomboxes -->
  <entityname.boombox1>Country Boombox</entityname.boombox1>
  <entitydescription.boombox1>"Sweet Home Alabama" by Lynyrd Skynyrd.</entitydescription.boombox1>
  <entityname.boombox2>Virtual Boombox</entityname.boombox2>
  <entitydescription.boombox2>"Virtual Insanity" by Jamiroquai.</entitydescription.boombox2>
  <entityname.boombox3>Metal Boombox</entityname.boombox3>
  <entitydescription.boombox3>"Enter Sandman" by Metallica.</entitydescription.boombox3>
  <entityname.boombox4>Bandit Boombox</entityname.boombox4>
  <entitydescription.boombox4>Bandit Radio from "S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Clear Sky".</entitydescription.boombox4>
  <entityname.boombox5>Clown Boombox</entityname.boombox5>
  <entitydescription.boombox5>"Tintin on the Moon" by Jeroen Tel.</entitydescription.boombox5>
  <entityname.boombox6>Punk Boombox</entityname.boombox6>
  <entitydescription.boombox6>"Come Out and Play" by The Offspring.</entitydescription.boombox6>
  <entityname.boombox7>Sailor Boombox</entityname.boombox7>
  <entitydescription.boombox7>"Weigh, Hey and up She Rises" by The Irish Rovers.</entitydescription.boombox7>
  <!-- Scrap Chunk -->
  <entityname.scrapore>Scrap Chunk</entityname.scrapore>
  <entitydescription.scrapore>A chunk of scrap so dense and compact, it has become a man-made ore. Can be deconstructed into scrap.</entitydescription.scrapore>
  <!-- Sharpened Volcano Fragment -->
  <entityname.sharpenedvolcanofragment>Sharpened Volcano Fragment</entityname.sharpenedvolcanofragment>
  <entitydescription.sharpenedvolcanofragment>An axe-shaped piece of sharpened magmatic rock infused with incendium. Permanently scalding, will cause burns and set targets on fire.</entitydescription.sharpenedvolcanofragment>
  <!-- Displacer Cannon -->
  <entityname.displacercannon>Displacer Cannon</entityname.displacercannon>
  <entitydescription.displacercannon>Space-warping experimental weapon powered by rare alien materials. Be careful to not explode yourself!</entitydescription.displacercannon>
  <!-- Hazmat Suit -->
  <entityname.hazmatsuit>Hazmat Suit</entityname.hazmatsuit>
  <entitydescription.hazmatsuit>Class C hazmat suit infused with lead and steel for radiation protection. Gas mask protects against airborne contaminants, be them radioactive, chemical or biological.</entitydescription.hazmatsuit>
  <!-- Nukie Mask -->
  <entityname.jetmask>Nukie Mask</entityname.jetmask>
  <entitydescription.jetmask>A diving mask and a helmet! How efficient.</entitydescription.jetmask>
  <!-- Diving Helmet -->
  <entityname.divinghelmet>Diving Helmet</entityname.divinghelmet>
  <entitydescription.divinghelmet>A diving mask and a helmet! How convenient.</entitydescription.divinghelmet>
  <!-- Constable Helmet -->
  <entityname.constablehelmet>Constable Helmet</entityname.constablehelmet>
  <entitydescription.constablehelmet>A diving mask and a helmet! How british.</entitydescription.constablehelmet>
  <!-- Hard Hat -->
  <entityname.hardhat>Yellow Hard Hat</entityname.hardhat>
  <entitydescription.hardhat>Crucial to maintain a safe working environment. Keeps your head safe! Also has a built-in engineer's goggle to facilitate wiring.</entitydescription.hardhat>
  <entityname.hardhathead>Orange Hard Hat</entityname.hardhathead>
  <entitydescription.hardhathead>Crucial to maintain a safe working environment. Keeps your head especially safe with its ballistic fiber lining on the inside! Also has a built-in engineer's goggle to facilitate wiring.</entitydescription.hardhathead>
  <entityname.hardhatjanitor>White Hard Hat</entityname.hardhatjanitor>
  <entitydescription.hardhatjanitor>Crucial to maintain a safe working environment. Keeps your head safe!</entitydescription.hardhatjanitor>
  <!-- Emergency Mask -->
  <entityname.disposabledivingmask>Emergency Mask</entityname.disposabledivingmask>
  <entitydescription.disposabledivingmask>Disposable emergency oxygen mask. Also serves a medical purpose since it lowers oxygen low, helping keep patients with a critical status alive.</entitydescription.disposabledivingmask>
  <!-- Creepy Mask -->
  <entityname.creepymask>Creepy Mask</entityname.creepymask>
  <entitydescription.creepymask>Boo-hoo, when's the hurting stop?</entitydescription.creepymask>
  <!-- Backwards Cap (for gang members) -->
  <entityname.backwardscap>Ballistic Cap</entityname.backwardscap>
  <entitydescription.backwardscap>Only craftable by gang members. Appears to be a backwards cap and bandana, but is lined with a ballistic fiber. Thug life.</entitydescription.backwardscap>
  <!-- Storage Guntainer -->
  <entityname.toolboxgun>Storage Guntainer</entityname.toolboxgun>
  <entitydescription.toolboxgun>A portable guntainer for storing tools and supplies.</entitydescription.toolboxgun>
  <!-- Antique Revolver -->
  <entityname.antiquerevolver>Antique Revolver</entityname.antiquerevolver>
  <entitydescription.antiquerevolver>An old single-action handcannon. Despite the age, still packs a punch.</entitydescription.antiquerevolver>
  <!-- Foldable Shotgun -->
  <entityname.foldableshotgun>Foldable Shotgun</entityname.foldableshotgun>
  <entitydescription.foldableshotgun>An antique shotgun that manages to have both power and portability by being foldable.</entitydescription.foldableshotgun>
  <!-- 40mm Rubber Round -->
  <entityname.40mmrubberround>40mm Rubber Round</entityname.40mmrubberround>
  <entitydescription.40mmrubberround>Ammunition for grenade launcher. Less-lethal rubber round, does not explode.</entitydescription.40mmrubberround>
  <!-- 40mm Jumper Grenade -->
  <entityname.40mmjumpergrenade>40mm Jumper Grenade</entityname.40mmjumpergrenade>
  <entitydescription.40mmjumpergrenade>Ammunition for grenade launcher. Harmless explosive, useful for blast jumping.</entitydescription.40mmjumpergrenade>
  <!-- Shotgun Slug Breaching -->
  <entityname.shotgunslugbreaching>Breaching Slug</entityname.shotgunslugbreaching>
  <entitydescription.shotgunslugbreaching>A shotgun slug for breaching doors. Still lethal.</entitydescription.shotgunslugbreaching>
  <!-- Makeshift Flamer -->
  <entityname.makeshiftflamer>Makeshift Flamer</entityname.makeshiftflamer>
  <entitydescription.makeshiftflamer>Fire extinguisher can filled with a flammable substance. The irony of being set on fire with a fire extinguisher might be lost on the person burning.</entitydescription.makeshiftflamer>
  <!-- Pipe Gun -->
  <entityname.pipegun>Pipe Gun</entityname.pipegun>
  <entitydescription.pipegun>Two pipes, a simple trigger and a stock. Extremely cheap and fast to manufacture. Accepts any kind of cartridge.</entitydescription.pipegun>
  <!-- Separatist Rifle -->
  <entityname.separatistrifle>Separatist Rifle</entityname.separatistrifle>
  <entitydescription.separatistrifle>Only craftable by rebel leaders. Classic soviet 7.62x39mm design used by freedom fighters, terrorists or both depending on who you ask.</entitydescription.separatistrifle>
  <entityname.762magazine>Separatist Rifle Magazine</entityname.762magazine>
  <entitydescription.762magazine>Only craftable by rebel leaders. A magazine containing 30 rounds of soviet 7.62x39mm.</entitydescription.762magazine>
  <entityname.762round>Separatist Rifle Round</entityname.762round>
  <entitydescription.762round>A round of 7x62x39mm.</entitydescription.762round>
  <!-- Marksmen Rifle -->
  <entityname.marksmanrifle>Marksmen Rifle</entityname.marksmanrifle>
  <entitydescription.marksmanrifle>Only craftable by rebel leaders. Precision 7.62x39mm semi-automatic rifle. The right arm of the free world.</entitydescription.marksmanrifle>
  <!-- Tommy Gun -->
  <entityname.tommygun>Tommy Gun</entityname.tommygun>
  <entitydescription.tommygun>A 9mm convertion of an antique submachine gun usually associated with the mafia or any other lavish criminals. Bolsters an impressive rate of fire and fine finish.</entitydescription.tommygun>
  <entityname.pistoldrum>Tommy Gun Drum</entityname.pistoldrum>
  <entitydescription.pistoldrum>A magazine for the tommy gun containing 60 rounds of 9mm.</entitydescription.pistoldrum>
  <!-- UZI -->
  <entityname.uzi>UZI</entityname.uzi>
  <entitydescription.uzi>Only craftable by gang members. A very light 9mm submachine gun with a foldable stock. This bullet hose fires faster than you can count.</entitydescription.uzi>
  <!-- Pistol -->
  <entityname.pistol>Pistol</entityname.pistol>
  <entitydescription.pistol>A finely-crafted compact 9mm pistol designed for civilian use.</entitydescription.pistol>
  <entityname.pistolmagazine>Pistol Magazine</entityname.pistolmagazine>
  <entitydescription.pistolmagazine>A magazine for pistols containing 20 rounds of 9mm.</entitydescription.pistolmagazine>
  <entityname.pistolround>Pistol Round</entityname.pistolround>
  <entitydescription.pistolround>A round of 9mm</entitydescription.pistolround>
  <!-- Flare Gun -->
  <entityname.flaregun>Flare Gun</entityname.flaregun>
  <entitydescription.flaregun>A brass and steel flare pistol with a wood finish of a bygone era. Serves as well in a museum as in the hands of a fighter.</entitydescription.flaregun>
  <entityname.flaregunround>Flare Gun Round</entityname.flaregunround>
  <entitydescription.flaregunround>Ammunition for a flare gun. Unusually explosive, great for setting flammable targets on fire.</entitydescription.flaregunround>
  <!-- Whaling Gun -->
  <entityname.whalinggun>Whaling Gun</entityname.whalinggun>
  <entitydescription.whalinggun>A flintlock muzzle-loaded spear shooter. Accepts any harpoon, but requires specifically magnesium or phosphorus as a propellant. Does not work underwater.</entitydescription.whalinggun>
  <entityname.whalingspear>Whaling Harpoon</entityname.whalingspear>
  <entitydescription.whalingspear>A massive harpoon designed for hunting whales, but will of course kill nearly anything that isn't a whale just as well. Can only be fired out of a whaling gun.</entitydescription.whalingspear>
  <!-- Water Cannon -->
  <entityname.watercannon>Water Cannon</entityname.watercannon>
  <entitydescription.watercannon>Pumps in water, stores it and then fires it at a high pressure. Useful for crowd control, cleaning, extinguishing fires or for propulsion in the air or water. Requires a battery to fire and to refill.</entitydescription.watercannon>
  <!-- Baseball Bat -->
  <entityname.baseballbat>Baseball Bat</entityname.baseballbat>
  <entitydescription.baseballbat>Hard to stab a guy in the back when he's beating your head in.</entitydescription.baseballbat>
  <!-- Brass Knuckle -->
  <entityname.brassknuckle>Brass Knuckle</entityname.brassknuckle>
  <entitydescription.brassknuckle>Don't bring a gun to a fist fight or you may have the dishonor of being killed with your own firearm. Truly a fistful of frags.</entitydescription.brassknuckle>
  <!-- Barricade -->
  <entityname.barricade>Barricade</entityname.barricade>
  <entitydescription.barricade>Steel beam that can be attached to a wall to provide cover in a gunfight.</entitydescription.barricade>
  <entityname.barricadestatic>Barricade Static</entityname.barricadestatic>
  <entitydescription.barricadestatic>Steel beam that has been attached to a wall to provide cover in a gunfight.</entitydescription.barricadestatic>
  <!-- Blood Cultist Robes -->
  <entityname.bloodcultistrobes>Blood Cultist Robes</entityname.bloodcultistrobes>
  <entitydescription.bloodcultistrobes>Only craftable by cultists. A simple hooded garment that blood cultists regeneration, immunity to disease and revives them if they die. The robe also serves to conceal their identity whilst letting other fellows cultists recognize them as their own.</entitydescription.bloodcultistrobes>
  <!-- Life Essence -->
  <entityname.lifeessence>Life Essence</entityname.lifeessence>
  <entitydescription.lifeessence>A magically forever beating human heart with a red glow. Can be consumed by cultists to reset time pressure and heal..</entitydescription.lifeessence>
  <!-- Human Heart -->
  <entityname.humanheart>Human Heart</entityname.humanheart>
  <entitydescription.humanheart>A human heart. If it's still beating, it soon won't be. Can be used by trained doctors to treat bloodloss.</entitydescription.humanheart>
  <!-- Sacrificial Dagger -->
  <entityname.sacrificialdagger>Sacrificial Dagger</entityname.sacrificialdagger>
  <entitydescription.sacrificialdagger>Only craftable by cultists. A crooked dagger imbued with an eery magic. Cultists can use these on the dying or recently deceased to rip out their still beating life essence.</entitydescription.sacrificialdagger>
  <!-- The 1998 -->
  <entityname.the1998>The 1998</entityname.the1998>
  <entitydescription.the1998>Only craftable by cultists. A book containing old forbidden knowledge in an forgotten language. Harmless in the hands of most, but cultists will use these to convert others into one of them.</entitydescription.the1998>
  <!-- Marauder Shield -->
  <entityname.cultistshield>Marauder Shield</entityname.cultistshield>
  <entitydescription.cultistshield>Only craftable by cultists. Medieval shield used to close in the distance to ranged heathen. Often paired with a mace.</entitydescription.cultistshield>
  <!-- Marauder Mace -->
  <entityname.cultistmace>Marauder Mace</entityname.cultistmace>
  <entitydescription.cultistmace>Only craftable by cultists. Medieval mace commonly used my marauders to bash in the skulls of infidels. Often paired with a shield.</entitydescription.cultistmace>
  <!-- Pitchfork -->
  <entityname.cultistpitchfork>Pitchfork</entityname.cultistpitchfork>
  <entitydescription.cultistpitchfork>Only craftable by cultists. Medieval pitchfork useful for chasing heretics and poking them until their guts pour out.</entitydescription.cultistpitchfork>
  <!-- Goblin Crate -->
  <entityname.goblincrate>Goblin Crate</entityname.goblincrate>
  <entitydescription.goblincrate>Too small for even the most nimble of humans... but maybe a goblin could fit in there.</entitydescription.goblincrate>
  <!-- Goblin Mask -->
  <entityname.goblinmask>Goblin Mask</entityname.goblinmask>
  <entitydescription.goblinmask>Only craftable by goblins and trolls. A strange green mask that emanates a magical aura. What happens if it is put on?</entitydescription.goblinmask>
  <!-- Midazolam -->
  <entityname.midazolam>Midazolam</entityname.midazolam>
  <entitydescription.midazolam>Strong drug with healing properties, but due to it's composition, it causes alcohol poisoning and unconciousness.</entitydescription.midazolam>
  <!-- Gangster Spraycan -->
  <entityname.spraycan>Spraycan</entityname.spraycan>
  <entitydescription.spraycan>Only craftable by members of the gang associated with the color. Aluminum can full of paint for defacing public spaces. Spray contains a very noxious acidic substance, do not use it on someone's face.</entitydescription.spraycan>
  <!-- Gangster Crystal Meth -->
  <entityname.crystalmeth>Crystal Meth</entityname.crystalmeth>
  <entitydescription.crystalmeth>Only craftable by members of the gang associated with the color. Can be smoked with a captain's pipe to join a gang. All the benefits and health risks of smoking pipe tabacco and injecting meth.</entitydescription.crystalmeth>
  <!-- Nexsuit -->
  <entityname.nexsuit>Nexsuit</entityname.nexsuit>
  <entitydescription.nexsuit>Nexpharma proprietary suit exclusive to their elite paramilitary group, the Mobile Emergency Rescue and Combat Squad, or MERCS. In actuality, it's just a PUCS adapted for combat.</entitydescription.nexsuit>
</infotexts>